industrysourcing.com 2018-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Industry Sourcing

##  Ringier Privacy Policy for"[www.industrysourcing.com](http://www.industrysourcing.com/)" (Referred to as "Site" hereafter)

This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Site. **If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site.**  
By accessing and using this Site, you hereby agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

##  Personal Information

In order to respond to your questions, to fulfil your requests or to manage interactive functions like submitting magazines/e-newsletters, conference registration/comments etc., it may be necessary to ask for personal information.This may include your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may use this information to respond to your requests or to contact you via mail, e-mail or phone to inform you of new services or promotions we may offer. If you place a request for a product or a supplier, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process your request. However, unless compelled by applicable legislation, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except if necessary to answer your questions, to fulfil your requests or to manage interactive functions. You also hereby grant to Ringier Trade Media Ltd. the right to exchange any information provided by you between Ringier Trade Media Ltd.'s affiliates for the purposes mentioned before. As a registered user, you agree, that Ringier Trade Media Ltd. is entitled to use your contact details in business communications activities. Contact details are Phone numbers, Fax numbers, eMail address, Address, Name, Company Name, Department and Title.

In addition to the personal information that you may provide us, this Site may use technology that lets us collect certain technical information like your Internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, traffic patterns and the address of any referring websites.

To unsubscribe from the industrysourcing.com email newsletter, click on the unsubscribe link in the footer of the email or contact us here at [edm@ringiertrade.com](mailto:edm@ringiertrade.com).

##  Security

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper or hacker- proof", Ringier Trade Media Ltd. has endeavoured to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access or improper use of your personal information.

##  Accuracy of collected data

Ringier Trade Media Ltd., on its own initiative or at your request, will replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by Ringier Trade Media Ltd. in connection with the operation of this Site.

##  Visitor identification

From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as "cookies". By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to continue to improve our Site. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this Site. If you do not wish to receive cookies or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

##  Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this Site or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.

Copyright： Industrysourcing.cn，Industrysourcing.com are owned by Ringier Trade Media Ltd.  
Company Address:Unit 2305,23/F Nam Wo Hong Building,148 Wing Lok Street,Sheung Wan,Hong Kong
